



# zedagim tesfaye tantu

Date of birth: 02/08/1998 | Nationality: Ethiopian | Gender: Male |

Phone number: (+251) 924700390 (Mobile) | Email address:

<u>zedagimzed@gmail.com</u> | **Facebook:** 

https://www.facebook.com/profile.php/?id=100010620430846 | **Twitter:** 

https://twitter.com/home | Instagram:

https://www.instagram.com/indzed?igsh=MW4zZTlxbHM4OWZ5MA== | LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/zed9331

**Skype:** https://join.skype.com/invite/JiSvyalZwG2C

WhatsApp Messenger: +251924700390

Address: wolayta sodo, 30 sefer, 10000, arada, Ethiopia (Home)

#### ABOUT ME

With over 3 years of experience as a Project Engineer, author, and teacher, I even have honed my abilties in diverse domains. My technique to problem-fixing is both analytical and creative, permitting me to address demanding situations effectively. Whether running collaboratively or independently, I always supply results. Beyond my middle responsibilities, I took the initiative to lead a intellectual fitness and health task inside my organization. This enterprise aimed to beautify the running surroundings for my colleagues, emphasizing their standard welfare.

Meeting deadlines is ingrained in my paintings ethic. I take delight in making sure well timed final touch of each task and assignment I undertake.

#### EDUCATION AND TRAINING

04/06/2017 - 15/07/2022

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE DEGREE IN WATER RESOURCE AND IRRIGATION ENGINEERING WITH CGPA 3.87 OUT OF 4.0 Jigjiga University

Address Jigjiga, Ethiopia, 1020 | Website <a href="https://www.jju.edu.et/">https://www.jju.edu.et/</a>

# WORK EXPERIENCE

05/06/2021 – 01/07/2022 jigjiga ,ethiopia, Ethiopia

# LECTURER AND COORDINATOR HORN INTERNATIONAL COLLEGE

- 1. teaching given courses (26hours/week)
- 2. advising students to discover their unreleased potential and create their future.and think critically.
- 3. follow-up and motivate students.
- 4.planning and organizing events.
- 5.problem solving and conflict resolution.

02/01/2024 - CURRENT jigjiga, Ethiopia

LECTURER AND COORDINATOR JIGJIGA UNVERSAL INTERNATIONAL COLLEGE

working pertime in unversal college.

# **PROJECT MANAGER TABAKALIYA CONSTRUCTION**

As a Project Manager, my function contains a huge variety of responsibilities. commonly include:

- 1. Planning and defining mission scope, objectives, and deliverables
- 2. Creating mission timelines and schedules
- 3. Allocating sources and coping with mission budget
- 4. Identifying and coping with mission risks
- 5. Leading and coordinating mission crew members
- 6. Monitoring and reporting on mission progress
- 7. Communicating with stakeholders and coping with expectations
- 8. Managing modifications to mission scope and schedule
- 9. Ensuring mission fine and assembly mission goals)

# DIGITAL SKILLS

Microsoft Office | Microsoft Word | Microsoft Powerpoint | Skype | LinkedIn | Facebook Twitter Instagram | Social media (Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, Pinterest, YouTube, Telegram, LinkedIn)

#### LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): AMAHRIC

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	B1	B1	B2	B1	B2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

#### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

# **COMMUNICATION AND INTERPERSONAL SKILLS**

**Communication and interpersonal skills gained through leadership position** The benefit of powerful communique competencies provide alot of advantege and contributes higher relationships, teamwork, and normal profession growth and it upload cost to proportion complicated information.

Link https://www.tiktok.com/@zed247003? t=8jz3cM1s3gk& r=1

# **HOBBIES AND INTERESTS**

writing and publishing books. On June 19, 2022, he graduated with the primary book. The 2nd book became launched on September 17, 2023. These non secular and mental content material books have given younger humans quite a few suggestion and imaginative and prescient a good way to use their talents.

#### VOLUNTEERING

03/07/2022 - 06/11/2022 sodo, ethiopia

**building tomorrow together** the objectives of volunteering is to foster a sense of community, compassion, and empowerment through various volunteer activites ,By engaging in meaningful project, we strive to address local needs, promote social inclusion, and inspire others to join our cause.

Zedagim Tesfaye Tantu

Ethiopia, 18/02/2024